var questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: " Which of the following is correct about JavaScript?",
      answer: " All of the above",
      options: [
        "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java",
        "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language",
        "The general-purpose core of the language has been embedded in Netscape, Internet Explorer, and other web browsers",
        " All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Which of the following is correct about callbacks?",
      answer: "Both of the above",
      options: [
        " A callback is a plain JavaScript function passed to some method as an argument or option.",
        "Some callbacks are just events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered",
        "Both of the above.",
        "None of the above."
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: " Which built-in method returns the string representation of the number's value?",
      answer: " toString()",
      options: [
        "toValue()",
        "toNumber()",
        " toString()",
        " None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "  Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
      answer: "charCodeAt()",
      options: [
        "charAt()",
        "charCodeAt()",
        "concat()",
        "indexOf()"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Which of the following function of String object executes the search for a match between a regular expression and a specified string?",
      answer: "search()",
      options: [
        "concat()",
        "match()",
        "replace()",
        "search()"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "  Which of the following function of String object returns the primitive value of the specified object.",
      answer: "valueOf()",
      options: [
        " toString()",
        "toUpperCase()",
        "toLocaleUpperCase()",
        "valueOf()"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a superscript, as if it were in a <sup> tag?",
      answer: "sup()",
      options: [
        "sup()",
        "small()",
        "strike()",
        "sub()"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?",
      answer: "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
      options: [
        "JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java",
        "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
        "They both originated on the island of Java",
        "  None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: " Which of the following function of Array object reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
      answer: "reverse()",
      options: [
        "reverse()",
        "push()",
        "reduce()",
        "reduceRight()"
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?",
      answer: "join()",
      options: [
        "concat()",
        "join()",
        "pop()",
        "map()"
      ]
    }
  ];
